// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
      question: "Is prejudgment or forming an opinion before becoming aware of the relevant facts of a case",
      answer: "Prejudice",
      options: [
        "Prejudice",
        "Attitude",
        "Bias",
        "Judgment",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
      question: "A distinct combination of feelings, inclinations to act and beliefs",
      answer: "Attitude",
      options: [
        "Prejudice",
        "Attitude",
        "Bias",
        "Judgment",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
      question: "This refers to the attitude that all members of a particular gender",
      answer: "Gender Prejudice",
      options: [
        "Age Prejudice",
        "Sexual Orientation Prejudice",
        "Gender Prejudice",
        "Ethnic/Racial Prejudice",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
      question: "This happens when negative opinions, beliefs, or attitudes are held about people for the simple reason that they belong to a specific ethnic group",
      answer: "Ethnic/Racial Prejudice",
      options: [
        "Age Prejudice",
        "Sexual Orientation Prejudice",
        "Gender Prejudice",
        "Ethnic/Racial Prejudice",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
      question: " This is also called homophobia",
      answer: "Sexual Orientation Prejudice",
      options: [
        "Age Prejudice",
        "Sexual Orientation Prejudice",
        "Gender Prejudice",
        "Ethnic/Racial Prejudice",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
      question: "This reflects a prejudice against older adults",
      answer: "Age Prejudice",
      options: [
        "Age Prejudice",
        "Sexual Orientation Prejudice",
        "Gender Prejudice",
        "Ethnic/Racial Prejudice",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
      question: "This is the attitude that those in a certain economic class are inferior to another class",
      answer: "Class Prejudice",
      options: [
        "Age Prejudice",
        "Sexual Orientation Prejudice",
        "Class Prejudice",
        "Ethnic/Racial Prejudice",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
      question: "Is a disproportionate weight in favor of or against an idea or thing, usually in a way that is closed-minded, prejudicial, or unfair",
      answer: "Bias",
      options: [
        "Attitude",
        "Bias",
        "Discrimination",
        "Prejudice",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
      question: "This relates to bias caused by group or peer pressure",
      answer: "Conformity Bias",
      options: [
        "Conformity Bias",
        "Beauty Bias",
        "Halo Effect",
        "Horns Effects",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
      question: "This plays out in terms of other physical attributes a person may have",
      answer: "Beauty Bias",
      options: [
        "Conformity Bias",
        "Beauty Bias",
        "Halo Effect",
        "Horns Effects",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 11,
      question: "This happens when we see one great thing about a person and we let the halo glow of that significant thing affect our opinions of everything else about that person",
      answer: "",
      options: [
        "Conformity Bias",
        "Beauty Bias",
        "Halo Effect",
        "Horns Effects",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 12,
      question: "This is the direct opposite of the Halo effect. It is when we see one bad thing about a person and we let it cloud our opinions of his other attributes",
      answer: "Horns Effects",
      options: [
        "Conformity Bias",
        "Beauty Bias",
        "Halo Effect",
        "Horns Effects",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 13,
      question: "This happens when we want to surround ourselves with people we feel are similar to us",
      answer: "Similarity Bias",
      options: [
        "Similarity Bias",
        "Confirmation Bias",
        "Bandwagon Effect",
        "Gender Bias",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 14,
      question: "This refers to a bias when we look for evidence to back up our own opinions of a person",
      answer: "Confirmation Bias",
      options: [
        "Similarity Bias",
        "Confirmation Bias",
        "Bandwagon Effect",
        "Gender Bias",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 15,
      question: "This is the tendency to adopt a certain behavior, style, or attitude simply because everyone else is doing it",
      answer: "Bandwagon Effect",
      options: [
        "Similarity Bias",
        "Confirmation Bias",
        "Bandwagon Effect",
        "Gender Bias",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 16,
      question: "This is widely held set of implicit biases that discriminate against a gender",
      answer: "Gender Bias",
      options: [
        "Similarity Bias",
        "Confirmation Bias",
        "Bandwagon Effect",
        "Gender Bias",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 17,
      question: "Means to prejudge something",
      answer: "Point of View",
      options: [
        "Unfairness",
        "Point of View",
        "Prejudice",
        "Bias",
    ]
  },
{
    numb: 18,
      question: "Is based on judgment on a personal point of view",
      answer: "Bias",
      options: [
        "Unfairness",
        "Point of View",
        "Prejudice",
        "Bias",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 19,
      question: "Is a printed media text or an informative paper document often used for sharing and promotional material",
      answer: "Point of View",
      options: [
        "Unfairness",
        "Point of View",
        "Prejudice",
        "Bias",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 20,
      question: "The following are the types of prose Execpt:",
      answer: "",
      options: [
        "Prose Peotry",
        "Fiction",
        "Non Fiction",
        "Fable",
    ]
  },

  // you can make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];